niba.com 2004-10-13

# MRA's Online Privacy Statement

**MRA's Online Privacy Statement**

MRA's web site is a valued membership benefit and we are committed to protecting the privacy of our site visitors. We provide protection under the umbrella of our privacy policy and practices.

**Unique Identifiers** , such as member numbers, usernames and passwords are collected from visitors to verify users' identity and control access to the "Members Only" section of the site.

**To Request More Information or Register for Training** many pages include forms which may require contact information, unique identifiers and credit card numbers. This information is used solely to meet the visitor's request. While visitors may be offered the opportunity to receive promotional materials and newsletters, they may decline these services at any time.

MRA does not disseminate information obtained about site visitors to any third party.

**Public Forums** are an MRA service and provide opportunity for professional networking via chat rooms and message boards. It is important that visitors maintain awareness that all information posted and disclosed in these areas is public information. Please exercise caution when disclosing personal or confidential information.

MRA reserves the right to monitor and remove any online communication deemed, in its sole discretion, to be unacceptable.

**Traffic information** is collected using only IP addresses. Cookies are used to help visitors to navigate the site's secure sections without re-entering a password.

**Links to other Web Sites** are provided for visitor convenience and should not be construed as an endorsement of those sites or as a guarantee that information available on the sites is accurate. MRA has no control over any external sites.

**Change in Terms of Privacy** is a right MRA reserves and all changes will be posted on this page. For MRA members, this privacy statement is a supplement to, not a replacement for, any other privacy agreements or terms already provided by MRA.

Use the **Contact Us** link located on each page if you have any comments or questions about the privacy statement, practices of this site, or your experience while visiting.
